# M AFIFUDIN ABDULLAH

+62822646166700 | work.afifudin@gmail.com | linkedin.com/afifudin | afifcodes.vercel.app

Nganjuk, East Java

I have over 3 years of experience in Front-End Development, 1+ year of experience in Flutter Development, and 4+ years of coding experience in general. Additionally, I possess basic knowledge of UI/UX Design using Figma. I am also interested in Full-Stack Development using Next.js, and I have experience using it for my Front-End projects. However, my current focus is on Front-End Development. I am currently a Computer Science student at Trunojoyo Madura University and have been working part-time as a Freelancer.

### **Education Level**

#### Trunojoyo Madura University - Madura, East Java

Aug 2019 - Feb 2024 (Expected)

Undergraduate in Computer Science, 3.50/4.00

- Engaged in research with the professor related to COVID-19 detection.
- Involved in research with the professor related to corn leaf disease detection.
- I'm not actively participating in competitions but am focused on developing my soft skills and building relationships by joining organizations.

# **Work Experiences**

Freelance - Remote Aug 2022 - Present

Web, Desktop, and Mobile Developer

- Collaborate with lecturers' research on Covid-19 detection to develop elegant web, desktop, and mobile applications named "Unvolds", tailored for use by radiologists.
- Engaging in partnerships with universities, as well as collaborating with BackEnd and UI/UX designers, to craft an exclusive travel application named "Lenjhelenan", dedicated to Madura Island.
- Collaborate with lecturers' research on corn leaves disease detection to develop mobile applications named "Dovtron".
- Creating a web application named "LabTI" for laboratory information, borrowing, and automated email borrowing management.

## **Organisational Experience**

### Laboratory Assistant - Trunojoyo Madura University

Feb 2022 - Present

• Contributing to the maintenance of computers and resolving network errors, while also being on standby as an administrator in the laboratory.

### **KOELIT** - Trunojoyo Madura University

Aug 2021 - Present

Fasilitator

· Conducting a webinar on Linux introduction.

#### Practical Assistant - Trunojoyo Madura University

Aug 2021 - Jan 2023

• Teaching students based on practical modules, assisting students with assignments or reports, and creating assignments.

### Skills, Achievements & Other Experience

- · Hard Skills: Front-End React.js
- Hard Skills: Web Next.js
- Hard Skills: Mobile Flutter
- · Hard Skills: Desktop Flutter
- Hard Skills: Web API Google Cloud
- Hard Skills: Laravel 8 & 9